[
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "ni",
    "questionDetails": "Ni fuma ni bebe or.",
    "answer": "nor, neither",
    "answerDetails": "He neither drinks nor smokes."
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "solo",
    "questionDetails": "El quedarse callado solo los hace mas fuertes.",
    "answer": "only, just, alone",
    "answerDetails": "Silence only makes them stronger."
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "nunca",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Nunca más!.",
    "answer": "never",
    "answerDetails": "Never again!."
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "verdad",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos este llamamiento constante para oraciones más duras y la verdad en la sentencia.",
    "answer": "truth, right, am i",
    "answerDetails": "We have this constant call for tougher sentences and truth in sentencing."
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "nosotros",
    "questionDetails": "Le pedimos que viniera con nosotros.",
    "answer": "us",
    "answerDetails": "We asked him to come with us."
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "tres",
    "questionDetails": "Tienen tres días para irse.",
    "answer": "three",
    "answerDetails": "You have three days to get out."
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "estás",
    "questionDetails": "Noté que estás usando titanio.",
    "answer": "‘re, re",
    "answerDetails": "I notice you’re using titanium."
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "puedo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Puedo ver esa revista por un momento?",
    "answer": "can i, may i, i am able",
    "answerDetails": "Can I see that magazine for a minute?"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "question": "ir",
    "answer": "ride"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "question": "tener",
    "questionDetails": "Ella va a tener un bebé.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "She’s going to have a baby."
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "question": "tu",
    "questionDetails": "Dime, hermosa doncella, cómo podré ganar tu Amor.",
    "answer": "thy",
    "answerDetails": "Tell me, fair maiden, how I may win thy love."
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "question": "gente",
    "questionDetails": "Él es mucho un hombre de la gente.",
    "answer": "people",
    "answerDetails": "He is very much a man of the people."
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "question": "decir",
    "questionDetails": "¿Jura decir la verdad?",
    "answer": "tell",
    "answerDetails": "Do you swear to tell the truth?"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "question": "estamos",
    "answer": "we are"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "question": "mis",
    "questionDetails": "El cine era en su origen de mis tíos.",
    "answer": "my",
    "answerDetails": "The cinema originally belonged to my aunt and uncle."
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "question": "soy",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quién eres?-¿Quién soy yo? Soy el presidente de tu universidad.",
    "answer": "am i, i am",
    "answerDetails": "Who are you?-Who am I? I’m the president of your college."
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "question": "entonces",
    "questionDetails": "No podemos usar ese nombre para nuestro restaurante.-Entonces, ¿qué piensas de llamarlo “El Agave”?",
    "answer": "in that case",
    "answerDetails": "We can’t use that name for our restaurant.-In that case, what do you think of calling it “El Agave”?"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "question": "casa",
    "questionDetails": "Las Casas de Lancaster y York pelearon en la guerra de las Dos Rosas.",
    "answer": "house, company, place",
    "answerDetails": "The Houses of Lancaster and York battled in the War of the Roses."
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "question": "después",
    "questionDetails": "Ella miró después de él.",
    "answer": "after, later, next",
    "answerDetails": "She stared after him."
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "question": "poco",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos un poco de ayuda de un esquema de entrenamiento.",
    "answer": "little, some, slightly",
    "answerDetails": "We got a little help from a training scheme."
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "favor",
    "questionDetails": "¡ No te olvides de darle las gracias por ofrecerse a hacerte el favor!.",
    "answer": "favour",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t forget to thank him for offering to do you a favour!."
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "tan",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy tan hambriento. Llevo horas sin comer.",
    "answer": "so, such, just",
    "answerDetails": "I’m so hungry. I haven’t eaten in Hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "nadie",
    "questionDetails": "No había nadie allí.",
    "answer": "anyone, anybody, none",
    "answerDetails": "There wasn’t anyone there."
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "antes",
    "questionDetails": "Trotando a través de la ciudad con guardias corriendo antes y detrás.",
    "answer": "before, first, earlier",
    "answerDetails": "Trotting through the city with guards running before and behind."
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "años",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo 25 años.",
    "answer": "years old",
    "answerDetails": "I’m 25 years old."
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "vas",
    "questionDetails": "Si vas al supermercado, acuérdate de comprar leche.",
    "answer": "you go, you are going",
    "answerDetails": "If you go to the grocery store, remember to buy milk."
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "van",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños van al parque todos los días después de la escuela.",
    "answer": "(they) go",
    "answerDetails": "The children go to the park every day after school."
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "mismo",
    "questionDetails": "Que ha trabajado en el mismo lugar durante unos cuantos años.",
    "answer": "same, very, as much",
    "answerDetails": "He’s worked at the same place for quite a few years."
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "hoy",
    "questionDetails": "Pero hoy, no tenemos tiempo para esto.",
    "answer": "today",
    "answerDetails": "But today, we have no time for this."
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "desde",
    "questionDetails": "La peor caída de la propiedad desde la guerra.",
    "answer": "since, from",
    "answerDetails": "The worst property slump since the war."
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "question": "quiere",
    "questionDetails": "Es su hijo y lo quiere, de modo que lo va a apoyar cueste lo que cueste.",
    "answer": "he loves him",
    "answerDetails": "He’s his son, and he loves him, so he’ll support him, whatever it takes."
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "sus",
    "questionDetails": "Que hagan sus propias llamadas.",
    "answer": "their",
    "answerDetails": "Have them make their own calls."
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "toda",
    "questionDetails": "El agua es la fuente de toda vida.",
    "answer": "all, whole, entire",
    "answerDetails": "Water is the source of all life."
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "cosa",
    "questionDetails": "En Denver este fin de semana se pueden hacer un montón de cosas.",
    "answer": "thing",
    "answerDetails": "There are a lot of things to do this weekend in Denver."
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "sea",
    "questionDetails": "Es probable que la parálisis sea permanente.",
    "answer": "be, ‘s, either",
    "answerDetails": "The paralysis will likely be permanent."
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "momento",
    "questionDetails": "El momento de la verdad para la mayoría de los niños alemanes viene al final del grado 4.",
    "answer": "moment, point, minute",
    "answerDetails": "The moment of truth for most German children comes at the end of Grade 4."
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "menos",
    "questionDetails": "Que este es un estereotipo positivo lo hace no menos un estereotipo.",
    "answer": "less, least, fewer",
    "answerDetails": "That this is a positive stereotype makes it no less a stereotype."
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "cuenta",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo una cuenta corriente y una cuenta de ahorro con el mismo banco.",
    "answer": "account, check, he tells",
    "answerDetails": "I have a checking account and a savings account at the same bank."
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "da",
    "questionDetails": "Le gusta llevar ese traje. Le da seguridad en sí misma.",
    "answer": "it gives",
    "answerDetails": "She likes to wear that outfit. It gives her confidence."
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "ella",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Es ella!.",
    "answer": "her",
    "answerDetails": "It’s her!."
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "claro",
    "questionDetails": "La razón de la evasividad de Pedro fue de repente tan claro como el día.",
    "answer": "clear, light, pale",
    "answerDetails": "The reason for Peter’s evasiveness was suddenly as clear as day."
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "question": "mañana",
    "questionDetails": "Un toque de luz acercada mostró que la mañana estaba en su camino.",
    "answer": "morning",
    "answerDetails": "A hint of steely light showed that morning was on its way."
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "question": "días",
    "questionDetails": "Tienen tres días para irse.",
    "answer": "days, morning",
    "answerDetails": "You have three days to get out."
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "question": "unos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tienes unos minutos después de la clase para hablar?",
    "answer": "few",
    "answerDetails": "Do you have a few minutes after class to chat?"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "question": "sabe",
    "questionDetails": "No quiero que nadie sepa que me despidieron.-Lisa lo sabe, pero no se lo dirá a nadie.",
    "answer": "knows",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t want anyone to know that I was fired.-Lisa knows, but she won’t tell anyone."
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "question": "dije",
    "questionDetails": "Dije la verdad. Nunca miento.",
    "answer": "i told",
    "answerDetails": "I told the truth. I never lie."
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "question": "dice",
    "questionDetails": "¿No te divertiste con mi hermana? Me dice que no la volviste a llamar.",
    "answer": "she tells, says it",
    "answerDetails": "Did you not have fun with my sister? She tells me that you didn’t call her back."
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "question": "tenía",
    "questionDetails": "La cirugía debió posponerse porque tenía una infección.",
    "answer": "he had",
    "answerDetails": "The surgery had to be postponed because he had an infection."
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "question": "ha",
    "questionDetails": "Ha conocido a mucha gente viajando.",
    "answer": "you have",
    "answerDetails": "You have met a lot of people by traveling."
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "question": "hablar",
    "questionDetails": "Alguien tendrá que hablar con Lily.",
    "answer": "talk",
    "answerDetails": "Someone will have to talk to Lily."
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "question": "parece",
    "questionDetails": "Créeme, es mucho más fácil de lo que parece.",
    "answer": "it looks, it appears, she looks",
    "answerDetails": "Trust me, it’s a lot easier than it looks."
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "question": "gusta",
    "questionDetails": "¿Te gusta mi nuevo corte de pelo?-No, no me gusta. ¡ Me encanta!.",
    "answer": "like it",
    "answerDetails": "Do you like my new haircut?-No, I don’t like it. I love it!."
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "question": "alguien",
    "questionDetails": "Si quieres ser alguien, tienes que esforzarte.",
    "answer": "someone, somebody, anyone",
    "answerDetails": "If you want to be someone, you have to work at it."
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "question": "quería",
    "questionDetails": "Ella quería a su caballo más que a nadie en el mundo.",
    "answer": "she loved",
    "answerDetails": "She loved her horse more than anything in the world."
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "question": "muchas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuántas personas vinieron a la fiesta?-Muchas.",
    "answer": "lot",
    "answerDetails": "How many people came to the party?-A lot."
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "question": "donde",
    "questionDetails": "Donde hay fe, hay esperanza.",
    "answer": "where",
    "answerDetails": "Where there is faith there is hope."
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "question": "había",
    "questionDetails": "Había muchas goteras en el techo.",
    "answer": "there were",
    "answerDetails": "There were many leaks in the ceiling."
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "question": "mundo",
    "questionDetails": "¿por qué en el mundo no te revelas antes?",
    "answer": "world, globe, life experience",
    "answerDetails": "Why in the world did you not reveal yourself sooner?"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "question": "tanto",
    "questionDetails": "“Estoy cansada de bailar tanto”, dijo la novia.",
    "answer": "so much",
    "answerDetails": "“I’m tired from dancing so much,” said the bride."
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "question": "pasó",
    "questionDetails": "Puede ser que sea lo que me pasó a mi.",
    "answer": "happened, spent, passed",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe that’s what happened to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "question": "salir",
    "questionDetails": "Salir con alguien.",
    "answer": "go out, exit",
    "answerDetails": "To go out with somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "question": "veces",
    "questionDetails": "Las nubes están raras. Si cae algo, unas veces es lluvia y otras veces es Nieve.",
    "answer": "sometimes, at times",
    "answerDetails": "The clouds are weird. If something falls, sometimes it’s rain and other times it’s snow."
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "question": "viene",
    "questionDetails": "A mí me encanta Harry Potter, pero mi mamá cree que viene del diablo.",
    "answer": "it comes, he is coming, are you coming",
    "answerDetails": "I love Harry Potter, but my mom thinks it comes from the devil."
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "question": "todas",
    "questionDetails": "Todas las personas que conocí.",
    "answer": "all",
    "answerDetails": "All the people I met."
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "question": "dar",
    "questionDetails": "Te daré una aspirina para reducir tu temperatura.",
    "answer": "bring, allow",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll give you an aspirin to bring down your temperature."
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "question": "tal",
    "questionDetails": "Lo llevó a tal estado.",
    "answer": "such",
    "answerDetails": "It took him to such state."
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "question": "hecho",
    "questionDetails": "De hecho.",
    "answer": "fact, done",
    "answerDetails": "In fact."
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "question": "pasar",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quieres pasar el fin de semana con nosotros?",
    "answer": "spend",
    "answerDetails": "Do you want to spend the weekend with us?"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "question": "noche",
    "questionDetails": "El jueves por la noche.",
    "answer": "night, evening",
    "answerDetails": "On Thursday night."
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "question": "igual",
    "questionDetails": "Todos nos tratamos como iguales.",
    "answer": "equal, alike, similar",
    "answerDetails": "We all treat each other as equals."
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "question": "estos",
    "questionDetails": "Glucosa se divide en dos de estos chicos.",
    "answer": "these",
    "answerDetails": "Glucose got split into two of these guys."
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "question": "cada",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy deseando ver a todos y cada uno de ustedes.",
    "answer": "each, every, such",
    "answerDetails": "I look forward to seeing each and every one of you."
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "question": "haciendo",
    "questionDetails": "Felipe logró pagar la deuda haciendo arte y vendiéndola.",
    "answer": "by making, by doing",
    "answerDetails": "Felipe was able to pay off the debt by making art and selling it."
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "question": "iba",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde está Leslie?-Me dijo que iba a la tienda.",
    "answer": "she was going, i was going",
    "answerDetails": "Where’s Leslie?-She told me she was going to the store."
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "question": "hombre",
    "questionDetails": "Es nuestro hombre en Moscú.",
    "answer": "man, male",
    "answerDetails": "He is our man in Moscow."
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "question": "saber",
    "questionDetails": "Saber hacer algo.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "To know how to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "question": "podemos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Estás seguro de que vamos a llegar a tiempo?-No te preocupes, podemos.",
    "answer": "we got this",
    "answerDetails": "Are you sure we’re going to make it on time?-Don’t worry, we got this."
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "question": "tienen",
    "questionDetails": "Mis padres vinieron de Guatemala a vivir conmigo en Canadá. Aunque tienen problemas para adaptarse a la cultura local, se sienten felices en su nuevo hogar.",
    "answer": "they are having",
    "answerDetails": "My parents came from Guatemala to live with me in Canada. Even though they are having problems adapting to the local culture, they feel happy in their new home."
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "question": "tú",
    "questionDetails": "Debes ir tú primero.",
    "answer": "you",
    "answerDetails": "You go out first."
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "question": "hola",
    "questionDetails": "Hola. ¿Cómo fue el vuelo?",
    "answer": "hi, hey, yo",
    "answerDetails": "‘Hi there. How was the flight?’."
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "question": "madre",
    "questionDetails": "La madre naturaleza.",
    "answer": "mother",
    "answerDetails": "Mother Nature."
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "question": "trabajo",
    "questionDetails": "Hiciste un muy buen trabajo en ese informe.",
    "answer": "job, labour, employment",
    "answerDetails": "You did a very good job with that report."
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "question": "fuera",
    "questionDetails": "Esperaremos fuera, para que nos puedas ver al llegar.",
    "answer": "outside, away",
    "answerDetails": "We will wait outside, so you can see us when you arrive."
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "question": "mira",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Mira! ¡ No pises el césped!.",
    "answer": "hey, take a look, she watches",
    "answerDetails": "Hey! Don’t step on the grass!."
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "question": "dijo",
    "questionDetails": "Le dijo al periodista que se había reunido con un agente del gobierno ruso.",
    "answer": "he told, you told, did you say",
    "answerDetails": "He told the reporter that he had met with an agent of the Russian government."
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "question": "digo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué a ti te hace caso cuando le dices algo y a mí no?-Porque lo digo con más firmeza.",
    "answer": "i say it, i mention it",
    "answerDetails": "Why does he pay attention to you when you say something but not to me?-Because I say it more firmly."
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "question": "tus",
    "questionDetails": "Pon tus atenciones en nuestro hijo.",
    "answer": "your",
    "answerDetails": "Set your attentions towards our child."
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "question": "buena",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Buena!-Gracias. Mi hermano me enseñó esa jugada.",
    "answer": "nice one",
    "answerDetails": "Nice one!-Thank you. My brother taught me that play."
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "question": "seguro",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvo que revisar su diario para estar seguro del día de la semana.",
    "answer": "sure, safe, insurance",
    "answerDetails": "She had to check her diary to be sure of the day of the week."
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "question": "mal",
    "questionDetails": "Que estaba mal de mí.",
    "answer": "wrong, evil, poorly",
    "answerDetails": "That was wrong of me."
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "question": "ellos",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente necesito hablar con Ellos.",
    "answer": "them, they",
    "answerDetails": "I really need to talk to them."
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "casi",
    "questionDetails": "Son casi las 6.",
    "answer": "almost, nearly, hardly",
    "answerDetails": "It’s almost 6 o’clock."
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "entre",
    "questionDetails": "No puedes comerte los dos, tienes que elegir entre el chocolate y el Helado.",
    "answer": "between, among",
    "answerDetails": "You can’t have both, you have to choose between the chocolate bar or the ice cream."
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "conmigo",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes hacer lo que quieras conmigo.",
    "answer": "me",
    "answerDetails": "You can do anything you want to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "único",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos que hacer un pago único.",
    "answer": "single, only",
    "answerDetails": "We need to make a single payment."
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "veo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tuviste noticias de Marisa Últimamente?-A veces la veo caminando en el parque.",
    "answer": "i see her",
    "answerDetails": "Have you heard anything about Marisa lately?-I see her sometimes walking in the park."
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "hora",
    "questionDetails": "Es hora de que nos vayamos.",
    "answer": "time, hour",
    "answerDetails": "It is time we left."
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "cinco",
    "questionDetails": "El jurado tardó cinco minutos.",
    "answer": "five",
    "answerDetails": "The jury was out five minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "siento",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Lo siento! No fue mi intención chocar contra ti.",
    "answer": "sorry",
    "answerDetails": "Sorry! I didn’t mean to bump you."
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": "dejar",
    "questionDetails": "Dejar a alguien hacer algo.",
    "answer": "leave, let, quit",
    "answerDetails": "To leave somebody to do something."
  }
]